<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WoTips</string>
    <string name="bannerAdd">ca-app-pub-1273779759756778/7177963006</string>
    <string name="intAdd">ca-app-pub-1273779759756778/2551063104</string>
    <string name="strAbout">Women’s security and women’s safety in today’s society has been an enduring subject from the time when the first girl appeared on the face of the Mother Earth. So what can we do? How can we ensure safety for women? Well, all we can do is accept the fact and take hands-on steps to improve our safety. Taking the above-stated safety tips for women to protect you will severely lessen your chances of becoming a prey of crime against women.\n\nStay alert of your surroundings! Take defensive measures and follow these safety tips for women to prevent crime against you and protect yourself. In fact, I would encourage you to pass this important message on to all women you know. Not just to your family and friends, but to one and all. All of us need to hear it. For you and to share with your precious ones, particularly the women.</string>
    <string-array name="strHeading">
        <item>Always be attentive</item>
        <item>Set your boundaries and impose them</item>
        <item>Use your cell phone smartly.</item>
        <item>Avoid danger zones</item>
        <item>Project your self-confidence</item>
        <item>If somebody tries to force you to an out-of-the-way place, do not go</item>
        <item>Watch your use of social media</item>
        <item>The Cyberspace can be a global spider’s web.</item>
        <item>Participate in a self-defence program</item>
        <item>Avoid travelling on your own</item>
        <item>Don’t be afraid to hurt somebody’s feelings</item>
        <item>Use common sense.</item>
        <item>Carry pepper spray with you.</item>
        <item>Don’t drink lest you have a decent mate</item>
        <item>Trust your instincts</item>
        <item>Don’t take up that ‘it’ can’t happen to you.</item>
        <item>Run, Lady, Run!</item>
        <item>Never, ever give up!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="strValue">
        <item>One of the most important safety measures for women’s protection is always to be attentive while you’re out-of-doors. Don’t lose your head in dreaming while you’re walking on the roads, driving, or eating anywhere. Don’t allow anything to keep you from noting your surroundings. Always be conscious of everything that is taking place near or around you. Keep a close look at the person who’s relentlessly throwing glimpses on you. With this, I don’t mean that you need to call the cops each time you notice someone observing you. Of course, there is a massive difference between being watchful and being insecure.</item>
        <item>If somebody tries to come too close to you for comfort, ask him or her to move back and force him or her to offer you your space. Don’t care about whether you’ll stumble upon as offensive or ill-mannered. Hark back to the fact that danger is likely to creep around in the shadows. So, stick to well-lit areas. If your security is at stake, it’s not the time to be pleasant.</item>
        <item>Yes, if you can use your phone appropriately, you don’t even have to care for other safety tips for women. Save the contact numbers of your family and friends on speed dial. Make certain that your mobile phone is completely charged. Save the numbers of police stations, women helplines and ambulances and keep them handy. There are quite a lot of provisions accessible such as safety alarms and auto dialing your friends or family. Make sure that you download the women safety apps that allow safety for women by tracking your movements.</item>
        <item>Now what are danger zones? Danger zones are those places where you are wide-open to assaults or burglary. Always try to use public transport and avoid taxis if possible. Carry on a poised attitude and don’t provide any signals of encouragement. If possible, try not going out late at nights and avoid dark lanes. I know that sounds silly, but that’s one of the best safety tips for women that works!</item>
        <item>What confidence has to do with safety tips for women? Well, if you look confident and self-possessed, harassers won’t like messing up with you. Dredge up that predators look for weak targets. You see, if you walk self-assuredly, people get the hint that you’re somebody that they cannot mess with. If you’re someone who always looks like an easy target, you will end up being an eventual aim for offences.\nCommunicate convincingly. It would be amazing if you can hold onto a top notch personality. It is imperative so that you give the impression of being strong and powerful. So, show your confidence while you walk on the roads or converse with people. Carry yourself with poise. Chin up! Back straight! Look every individual into the eye.</item>
        <item>Research shows that if people have a plan to force you to an out-of-the-way place, then they might have plans not to let you make it out alive as well. Whatsoever you do, don’t ever get in a car with anyone irrespective of what they say.  It’s not going to be upright for you.</item>
        <item>Some girls put the whole she-bang of their life on Facebook. With this, I mean everything from what they ate for lunch to what they are wearing at the moment. Dredge up that the more data you give out on social media, the more somebody else will know about your schedule.  And guess what? It will let an offender figure out when you’re most helpless. So, don’t forget to set in some internet safety tips in your lifestyle as well</item>
        <item>Please, please, please… I request you to be alert to the risks of entering into on-line relationships. Keep an eye on the on-line safety tips to ensure your general security in the cyber world. Don’t provide a lot of personal information such as your phone numbers and address to anyone. If you decide on meeting someone face to face with, then take a friend along.</item>
        <item>Learning self-defence strategies is one of the most appealing safety tips for women. It’s a good way to defend you. You can register for the martial arts training course to absorb some fighting tactics like Tai Chi, Kung Fu, Taekwondo, Judo, Karate, and the like. Likewise, you can learn from the comfort of your home by viewing some self-defence videos on YouTube. Try to absorb a martial art form to beat off any physical attack.\nAnd yes, here I’d like to give you a tiny tip from my personal experiences. Summon up that the most delicate point in a man’s body is generally – not his groin but his eyes. You can always kick the attacker in the groin and run away. But putting pressure on his eyes will furthermore be of super value.</item>
        <item>This piece of suggestion is rather of no use as at times; you have no other choice than to travel alone, though it bears talking about. I know that it may not seem fair or reasonable, but simply having a man as a partner while travelling can save you a lot of suffering.</item>
        <item>If you find yourself in an awkward position, it is okay to raise your voice and be rude. You can be discourteous if you have to. Be brave. If you feel like someone is following you, look the man right into his eye and ask him why. You could make an apology well ahead if your instincts were off beam. But you cannot reverse the effects of assault if your gut feeling was right but you didn’t act on them.\nIt’s okay NOT to be a good girl and friendly all the time. With strangers, it’s safer to be cold and reserved. Women are sympathetic and giving by nature, which can get them in a lot of dangerous situations. Teach your children to be suspicious of strangers, too.</item>
        <item>Out of all the essential safety tips for women, using your common sense is an absolute conqueror. It can aid you in guarding yourself in far more ways than you can conjure up. Avoid walking on dark streets. Stay away from unsafe regions, and don’t display your cash or jewels when out-of-door.</item>
        <item>A pepper spray in your handbag can protect you in the case of an assault. In India, these sprays are easily obtainable at chemist’s shop. In western countries, people use certain girl safety products and protective devices such as electric guns as well. Perhaps, you can order them from on-line stores. Besides, you can always carry chilli powder; it’s as useful as a pepper spray. Just spray the stuff in the eyes of the enemy and run away.</item>
        <item>If you’re out at a social occasion, bar, cafe, get-together, or any celebration, always keeps in mind: Drinking alcohol may worsen your natural defences and make you an easy target. I’d advise you not to drink lest you have a clear-headed and a pleasant companion with you for the night. And, to drive you back home, of course. Always keep an eye on what you’re drinking – Roofies happen you see!</item>
        <item>One of the paramount safety tips for women is learning to trust your instincts.  If a position doesn’t feel right, it perhaps isn’t. Get out of it as soon as you can! Believe me, 90 percent of the time, a woman’s instincts are right. So when your heart tells you to get out of the situation, do it immediately. Be conscious of your backgrounds. Have faith in your gut feelings. If something or somebody feels off the beam, believe your sixth sense. Don’t do it! Don’t go there!</item>
        <item>“It” can happen to anybody, any place and at any time. So, don’t presume that “it” can’t happen to you. Learn about self-defence and women safety. In fact, the quest for women’s security doesn’t end here! Explain your daughters, friends, mom’s, grandmas, friends, co-workers, sister and every single woman you know what you learn about self-defence and survival instinct.</item>
        <item>Practice running! It, in fact, it is one of the most important female safety tips. You can begin with running for a short distance. Why? See, if you run on no occasion, then you won’t ever be sure that you can if you have to. Running away proves to be a cherished self-protection tool. So, Run, Lady, Run! Even if the aggressor has a gun pointed at you, run as fast as you can for your life!</item>
        <item>Last but not least, never give up, no matter what happens! In fact safety tips for women are all about not losing hope, giving the free rein to your inner b**ch and letting her go! If you’re fighting the battle for your life, make certain that you’re the champ. It’s just the right time to play the dirty game of life and death and let the cards fall where they must. Or else, following any of the above safety tips for women is purposeless!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_tips">TipsActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
